owenscorning.com 2018-11-25

# Privacy Policy | Owens Corning

## Owens Corning's Internet Privacy Statement

Owens Corning respects the privacy of every individual who visits our web site, sends us e-mail or responds to our interactive advertisements. This Privacy Statement states how Owens Corning will collect, use and disclose information it collects from you. This Privacy Statement may be changed at any time, and Owens Corning will notify you of any such changes by posting an updated version of the Privacy Statement on this page of the web site.

## Personally-Identifiable Information

There are several opportunities on our web site for you to provide us with personally-identifiable information about you (such as name, mailing address and e-mail address) and your interests. If you choose to share any personal information with us, we may store it and use it to provide you with an individualized user experience and for marketing research and other marketing purposes. This may include sharing it with other companies in the Owens Corning family, our third-party business partners, and/or our third-party business consultants and providers (collectively, "Providers") so that they may contact you for direct marketing purposes, including offers of discounts on services.

## Non-Personal Information

Sometimes, we may collect non-personal information about you that is anonymous data. The information we receive is for Owens Corning's use only and is not disclosed to any other party except in aggregate form. Examples of this information include the length and time of your visit, the pages you looked at on our site, the type of Internet Browser you have and the site you visited just before coming to ours. We use this information to develop ideas for improving our site and to measure site activity. This may include sharing it with our Providers.

## Cookies

Our web site makes use of "cookie" files to customize information to your personal tastes. A cookie is an element of data that a web site can send to your Browser, which may store some information on your computer. Then, when you come back to our site or visit other websites, information can be tailored to suit your individual preferences. The goal is to save you time and provide you with a more meaningful online experience. Most Internet Browsers will allow you to erase cookies from your computer hard drive, block all cookies or receive a warning before a cookie is stored. Please refer to your Browser instructions to learn more about these functions.

## Cookie Policy

We use cookies and tracking technologies on our website. Functionalities may include:

* \- Assisting you in navigation
* \- Assisting your use of our products, services and applications
* \- Assisting with our promotional and marketing efforts
* \- Providing content from third parties

We classify our cookies in following categories:

* Strictly Necessary Cookies:  
These cookies are necessary for the website to function and cannot be switched off in our systems. They are usually only set in response to actions made by you which amount to a request for services, such as setting your privacy preferences, logging in or filling in forms. You can set your browser to block or alert you about these cookies, but some parts of the site will not then work. These cookies do not store any personally identifiable information. 

* Performance Cookies:  
These cookies allow us to count visits and traffic sources so we can measure and improve the performance of our site. They help us to know which pages are the most and least popular and see how visitors move around the site.

* Functional Cookies:  
These cookies enable the website to provide enhanced functionality and personalisation. They may be set by us or by third party providers whose services we have added to our pages.

* Targeting Cookies:  
These cookies may be set through our site by our advertising partners. They may be used by those companies to build a profile of your interests and show you relevant adverts on other sites.

## European Privacy Policy

Click here to view

## Third Parties

Owens Corning may establish relationships with reputable business partners that allow visitors to our site to navigate directly to sites operated by these partners. We choose our business partners carefully. However, Owens Corning is not responsible for the content or privacy practices of third party web sites that may be linked to on this site. These links are meant for the user's convenience only and do not constitute sponsorship, endorsement, or approval by Owens Corning of the content, policies, or practices of such sites nor any products or services which may be offered through that site. Once you have left the Owens Corning site via such a link, you should check the applicable Privacy Statement of the third party site.

We are currently using certain third party tools on our website and may, in the future, implement additional analytics tools. Data collected as a result of our use of such tools, however, is only used internally to enhance our users’ experience using our website and for our own internal business purposes. Such data may be shared with our partners and advertisers, if at all, only as aggregate information and as otherwise specified in this privacy policy. Please contact us if you have any specific questions regarding our use of analytics or other analytics tools.

Currently, (i) other parties (e.g. third-party advertising networks and analytics providers) may collect personal information about your online activities over time and across different websites when you use our website or services, and (ii) we do not respond to, or take any specific action in connection with the receipt of, Do-Not-Track signals or other similar mechanisms regarding the collection of personally identifiable information about an individual consumer’s online activities over time and across third-party websites or online services.

Under California Civil Code, California residents are entitled to ask us for a notice describing what categories of personal customer information we share with third parties or corporate affiliates for those third parties or corporate affiliates' direct marketing purposes. If you are a California resident and want a copy of this notice, please submit a written request to the following address:

Owens Corning

C/o Get Pink

One Owens Corning Pkwy

Toledo, OH 43659

In your request, please specify that you want a California Privacy Rights Notice. Please allow 45 days for a response.

## Security

Your personally identifiable information is one of our valuable assets. It is kept in a secure datacenter and is accessible only to authorized personnel as needed to perform operations governed by this Privacy Statement. Please keep in mind that despite these measures, Owens Corning cannot guarantee or warrant 100% security of its servers and databases. Moreover, Owens Corning cannot guarantee that personally-identifiable information that you submit through the Site will not be intercepted.

## Children

Owens Corning has no intention of collecting any personal information from individuals under 18 years of age. If a child has provided us with personal information without the consent of a parent or guardian, a parent or guardian should contact us at [answers@answers.owenscorning.com](mailto:answers@answers.owenscorning.com) if they would like us to use reasonable effort to delete this information from our files.

## Contact Information and Access to Personally-Identifiable Information

You may review and change the personally-identifiable information associated with your account by logging in to your account and clicking the "Edit My Profile" link. If you do not want your personal information collected by Owens Corning or shared by Owens Corning with any Providers other than any affiliates of Owens Corning, or if you would like to delete your account, please contact Owens Corning at [answers@answers.owenscorning.com](mailto:answers@answers.owenscorning.com) and we will use reasonable efforts to delete your information from our files and will also use reasonable efforts to instruct any third party Provider to delete your information from its files. Please note, however, that your personally-identifiable information is the basis for your account and your election to not have it shared or collected will result in the deletion of your account.

Material changes to Owens Corning Internet Privacy Statement will be posted in this notice.

Last updated and effective as of March 10, 2016
